A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5 FA1403
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Painting and Sculpture, 1964-2007; 17; 32.95 Cubic Feet 87 containers
  - Malaysia, 17.9
    - Rashid, Anuar, B-8593(27)R, 1985 (Box 836, Folder 2)
    - Zubir, Sharifa Fatimah Syed, B-7729, B-7826, 1977; 1978 (Box 836, Folder 3-4)
    - Sitharan, Roopesh, 100-00-26143-203.3, 703-00-25119-203.1, 720-00-24106-203.1, 2004-2006 (Box 837, Folder 1)
  - Nepal, 17.10
    - Giri, Pramila, California State University-Long Beach, B-7425, B-7525, 1974-1975 (Box 837, Folder 2)
    - Nepal Association of Fine Arts, Painting Art Supplies, B-7258-AIP, B-7345-AIP, 1972-1973 (Box 837, Folder 3)
  - Pakistan, 17.11
    - Geoffrey, Iqbal, Other than Correspondence, B-6507, B-6402, 1964-1965 (Box 837, Folder 4)
    - Geoffrey-Jafree, J. Iqbal, Book #1 of 6, Correspondence, B-6402, B-6507, 1964 (Box 838, Folder 1)
    - Geoffrey-Jafree, J. Iqbal, Book #2 of 6, Correspondence, B-6402, B-6507, 1965 (Box 838, Folder 2)
    - Geoffrey-Jafree, J. Iqbal, Book #3 of 6, Correspondence, B-6402, B-6507, 1966 (Box 838, Folder 3)
    - Geoffrey-Jafree, J. Iqbal, Book #4 of 6, B-6402, B-6507, 1967-1969 (Box 838, Folder 4)
    - Geoffrey-Jafree, J. Iqbal, Book #5 from 1970, B-6402, B-6507 (Box 838, Folder 5)
    - Geoffrey-Jafree, J. Iqbal, Book #6 from 1971, B-6402, B-6507 (Box 838, Folder 6)
  - Philippines, 17.12
    - Joya, Jose, IIE, B-6774, DF-6965, 1967; 1969 (Box 839, Folder 1)
    - University of the Philippines, Printmaking Project, Joya, J., B-7160, DF-71120, 1971 (Box 839, Folder 2)
    - Rodriquez, Manuel, Jr., Pratt Graphic Center, B-7139, 1971 (Box 839, Folder 3)
    - Art in General, 703-00-21033-203.2, 2001 (Box 839, Folder 4)
    - Art in General, 100-00-99043-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 839, Folder 5)
    - Samba-Likhan, 100-00?99007-203.3, 1999 (Box 839, Folder 6)
    - Big Sky Mind Artists' Projects Foundation, 655-00-24021-203.2, 2004 (Box 839, Folder 7)
    - Cuison, Noel, 703-00-99024-203.2, 703-00-98103-203.1, 1999 (Box 840, Folder 1)
    - Del Rosario, Mariano, 494-00-96042-1, 1996 (Box 840, Folder 2)
    - Capucion, Erma L., 655-00-23093-203.1, 100-00-23121.3, 2003 (Box 840, Folder 3)
    - Evangelista, Maria Carina Lim, 706-00-24071-203.1, 2004 (Box 840, Folder 4)
    - Padilla, Letina, 703-00-26111-203.1, 2006 (Box 840, Folder 5)
    - Rivera, Alan, 703-00-94086-203.000-1, 100-00-95120-203.000-3, 1994 (Box 841, Folder 1)
    - Roldan, Amiel, 703-00-23107-203.1, 2003 (Box 841, Folder 2)
    - Salubayba, Don Maralit, 703-00-24109-203.1, 2004 (Box 841, Folder 3)
  - Singapore, 17.13
    - Eng Tow B-8525(27)R, 1985 (Box 843, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan, 17.14
    - Fong, Chung-Ray, B-7140, 1971 (Box 842, Folder 1)
    - Fong, Chung-Ray, B-7140, 1971 (Box 842, Folder 2)
    - Deng, Yau-Horng, 703-00-97105-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 842, Folder 3)
    - Lien, Te-Cheng, 703-00-94087-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 842, Folder 4)
    - Headlands Center for the Arts, 100-00-950112-203.000-3, 1995 (Box 842, Folder 5)
    - ARCUS, Wan-Chen Lee, 703-00-22126-203.1, 2002 (Box 843, Folder 1)
    - Chang, Yuan-Chien, 703-00-97108-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 843, Folder 2)
    - Chen, Hsing-Wan, 100-00-96001-203.000-3, 1996 (Box 843, Folder 3)
    - 18th Street Arts Complex, 703-00-20021-203.1, 2000 (Box 843, Folder 4)
    - 18th Street Arts Complex, 703-00-21034-203.2, 2001 (Box 843, Folder 5)
    - Headlands Center for the Arts, 703-00-20023-203.2, 2000 (Box 843, Folder 6)
    - Headlands Center for the Arts, Yu Wen-Fu, 703-00-22027-203.2, 2002 (Box 843, Folder 7)
    - Headlands Center for the Arts, Howard Chen, 703-00-21035-203.2, 2001 (Box 843, Folder 8)
    - Huang, Chih-Yang, 703-00-96094-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 843, Folder 9)
    - Huang, Chih-Yang, 703-00-96094-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 844, Folder 1)
    - Reasoner, Kathryn, 100-00-21007-203.3, 2001 (Box 844, Folder 2)
    - Wang, Te-Ho, 100-00-20123-203.3, 2001 (Box 844, Folder 3)
    - Yao, Jui-Chung, 703-00-97107-203.000-1, 1997 (Box 844, Folder 4)
    - ARCUS, Lin Chien-Jung, 703-00-24110-203.1, 2004 (Box 845, Folder 1)
    - Chang, Hsing-yu, 731-00-24117-203.1, 2004 (Box 845, Folder 2)
    - Hsiao, Sheng-Chien, 695-00-23113-203.1, 2003 (Box 845, Folder 3)
    - Huang, Lan-Ya, 750-00-25127-203.1, 2005 (Box 845, Folder 4)
    - Kanai, Yoshiko, 100-00-22067-203.1, 2002 (Box 634, Folder 3)
    - Lin, Jiun-Ting, 668-00-22154-203.4, 2002 (Box 845, Folder 5)
    - Wang, Ya-Hui, 749-00-25128-203.1, 730-00-24118-203.1, 2005 (Box 846, Folder 1)
    - Wu, Ta-Kun, 730-00-24137-203.4, 2004 (Box 846, Folder 2)
    - Yang, His-Hsia, 694-00-23114-203.1, 2003 (Box 846, Folder 3)
  - Thailand, 17.15
    - Srisouta, Praphan, B-7257, 1972 (Box 846, Folder 4)
    - Damrong, Wong-Uparaj, B-6879, DF-6922, EC-7021, 1968-1970 (Box 847, Folder 1)
    - Srisouta, Praphan, Cranbrook Academy of Art, EC-7131, B-7216, B-7257, B-7331, B-7430, 1971-1974 (Box 847, Folder 2)
    - Banchong Kosalwat, B-70101, 1970 (Box 943, Folder 7)
    - Arjunka, Pricha, Institute of International Education (IIE), DF-6892, DF-6895, DF-68101, B-6947, DF-7338, 1968-1973 (Box 847, Folder 3)
    - Kosalwat, Banchong, Pratt Institute, B-7044, B-70101, 1970 (Box 847, Folder 4)
    - Mekpayab Art Centre, EC-7481, 1974 (Box 847, Folder 5)
    - Damrong, Wong Uparaj, EC-7021, 1970 (Box 848, Folder 1)
    - Boonma, Montien, 703-00-95096-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 848, Folder 2)
    - Launcharoen, Prawat, B-7225, 1972 (Box 848, Folder 3)
    - Satsara, Supachai, B-93121(27), 1993 (Box 848, Folder 4)
    - Art in General, 634-00-22118-203.1, 2002 (Box 848, Folder 5)
    - Ko-Udomvit, Thavorn, R-8319(27), 1983 (Box 849, Folder 1)
    - Ko-Udomvit, Thavorn, R-8319(27), 1983 (Box 849, Folder 2)
    - Headlands Center for the Arts, P. Santipak, 703-00-20121-203.1, 2000 (Box 849, Folder 3)
    - Headlands Center for the Arts, Nuts Society, 703-00-22128-203.1, 2002 (Box 850, Folder 1)
    - Lekutai, Wanwarang, 703-00-97146-203.1, 1997 (Box 850, Folder 2)
    - Poshyananda, Apinan, EC-8808(27)R, 1988 (Box 850, Folder 3)
    - Rasdjarmrearnsook, Araya, 703-00-96096-203.000-1, 703-00-94107-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 850, Folder 4)
    - Rasdjarmrearnsook, Araya, 703-00-96096-203.000-1, 703-00-94107-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 851, Folder 1)
    - Suwannipa, Pakamas, 100-00-21013-203.3, 703-00-99103-203.1, 2001 (Box 851, Folder 2)
    - Gaweewong, G., 634-00-22114-203.1, 2002 (Box 851, Folder 3)
    - About Art Related Activities, 706-00-24072-203.1, 2004 (Box 851, Folder 4)
    - About Art Related Activities, 706-00-24072-203.1, 2004 (Box 852, Folder 1)
    - Puntusawasdi, Tawatchai, 703-00-21130-203.1, 2001 (Box 852, Folder 2)
    - Sitthiket, Vasan, 703-00-26024-203.2, 703-00-25121-203.1, 2006 (Box 852, Folder 3)
    - Somthai, Pitwat, 703-00-23109-203.1, 2003 (Box 853, Folder 1)
  - Vietnam, 17.16
    - Duchman, Nguyen, Institute of International Education (IIE), DF-6547, DF-6631, DF-6679, 1964-1966 (Box 853, Folder 2)
    - Indochina Arts Project, EC-9215(27), 1992 (Box 853, Folder 3)
    - Indochina Arts Partnership, 703-00-97148-203.1, 1997 (Box 853, Folder 4)
    - Art in General, 703-00-98104-203.1, 1998 (Box 853, Folder 5)
    - Indochina Arts partnership, 100-0098129-203.3, 1998 (Box 853, Folder 6)
    - ARCUS, Le Thua Tien, 703-00-23110-203.1, 2003 (Box 853, Folder 7)
    - Tran Van Thao, 703-00-21131-203.1, 2001 (Box 854, Folder 1)
    - Goethe Institut Hanoi, 718-00-25108-203.1, 2005 (Box 854, Folder 2)
    - Williamburg Art and Historical Center, 703-00-22129-203.1, 2002 (Box 854, Folder 3)
- Publications, 1964-1990; 18; 6.05 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes and 2 record storage boxes
  - Afghanistan, 18.1
    - Franklin Book Program, B-6665, 1966 (Box 854, Folder 4)
  - Asia, 18.2
    - Brooklyn Museum, Cultural Property Export, for ICOM, B-72103, 1972 (Box 854, Folder 5)
    - The Drama Review, NYU (TDR), Erika Munk, B-70108, B-7165, 1970-1971 (Box 854, Folder 6)
    - Artibus Asiae, B-6416, DF-6756, B-6779, B-6881, B-7163, B-7260, B-7348, B-7446, B-7537, B-7641, B-7741, B-7849, B-7939, DF-8024, 1964-1980 (Box 855, Folder 1)
    - Freer Gallery of Art, Ars Orientalis, B-7885, 1972 (Box 855, Folder 2)
    - University of Hawaii Press, DF-8414, 1984 (Box 855, Folder 3)
    - Asian Distribution of Bick Temples of Bengal, DF-8453, 1984 (Box 859, Folder 10)
    - Asian Theater Journal, DF-90108, 1990 (Box 855, Folder 4)
    - University of Hawaii Press, DF-8244, 1982 (Box 855, Folder 5)
    - Art International, 1980 March-April (Box 945, Folder 2)
  - Burma, 18.3
    - Old Burma-Early Pagan, B-6735, Museum Program, 1967 (Box 855, Folder 6)
    - Old Burma-Early Pagan, B-6735, Pagan, Land Rover, 1967 (Box 856, Folder 1)
    - Old Burma-Early Pagan, B-6735, Pagan, Guides, etc., 1967 (Box 856, Folder 2)
    - Old Burma-Early Pagan, B-6735, Pagan, Museum, 1967 (Box 856, Folder 3)
    - Old Burma-Early Pagan, B-6735, Pagan, Travel, Aung Thaw, 1967 (Box 856, Folder 4)
    - Old Burma-Early Pagan, B-6735, Pagan, General, 1967 (Box 856, Folder 5)
    - Old Burma-Early Pagan, B-6735, Pagan, Books Program, 1967 (Box 856, Folder 6)
    - Luce, Gordon, Other than Correspondence, B-6735, 1967 (Box 856, Folder 7)
    - NYU, Luce, G. H., B-6735, 1967 (Box 856, Folder 8)
    - Asian Distribution of Old Burma-Early Pagan (Box 857, Folder 1)
  - China, 18.4
    - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, Na, Chih-liang, B-7231, 1972 (Box 857, Folder 2)
    - Walters Art Gallery, Katz, Lois, Chinese Ceramics Catalog, B-7263, 1972 (Box 857, Folder 3)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, LIU, L. Y. S., EC-7764, B-7853, 1977-1978 (Box 857, Folder 4)
  - India, 18.5
    - Beattie, May H., Sawai Man Singh II Museum, India, B-7258-AIP, 1972 (Box 857, Folder 5)
    - Calico Textile Museum, Book Sales, Sarabhai Enterprises, B-7345-AIP, B-6727, B-6954, 1967-1973 (Box 857, Folder 6)
    - Calico Textile Museum, Other than Correspondence, Margaret Hall Contract and Book Notes, B-6727, B-6954, 1967-1969 (Box 857, Folder 7)
    - Calico Textile Museum, B-6954, 1969 (Box 945, Folder 1)
    - Calico Textile Museum, B-6727, B-6954, 1967-1969 (Box 857, Folder 8)
    - Vijayanagara Project Report, DF-8448, 1984 (Box 858, Folder 1)
  - Japan, 18.6
    - Roberts, Laurance P., DF-7595, 1975 (Box 858, Folder 2)
    - Weatherhill, John, Inc., EC-7598, 1975 (Box 858, Folder 3)
  - Pakistan, 18.7
    - Quraeshi, Samina, B-7258-AIP, 1972 (Box 858, Folder 4)
  - Tibet, 18.8
    - Newark Museum, Olson, Eleanor, B-7065, 1970 (Box 858, Folder 5)
  - Gallery Catalogues, 18.9
    - Sam Francis (Box 945, Folder 8)
    - Mutsuo Kawarabayashi (Box 945, Folder 8)
    - Hisayuki Mogami (Box 945, Folder 8)
    - Shin Kuno (Box 945, Folder 8)
    - Michio Fukuoka (Box 945, Folder 8)
    - Jiro Takamatsu (Box 945, Folder 8)
    - Minotu Kawabata (Box 945, Folder 8)
    - Park, Seo-Bo (Box 945, Folder 8)
    - Shoichi Ida (Box 945, Folder 8)
    - Bridget Riley (Box 945, Folder 8)
    - Toshinobu Onosato (Box 945, Folder 9)
    - Mansobu Yoshimura (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Kentaro Kimura (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Gutai Group (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Tadasky Kuwayama (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Yusuke Nakahara (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Onosato, Toshinobu (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Guiseppe Santomaso (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Gutai Pinacotheca (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Sizu Simada (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Yoshikuni Iida (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Mitsunobu Matsuo (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Haruhiko Yasuda (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Atsuko Tanka (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Koji Enokura (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Mitsuo Kano (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Charles Hinman Exhibition (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Kikuhata (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Inumaki, Kenji (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - A Catalogue of Antiquarian Remains of Afghanistan, Walter Spink (and Suresh Vasant) (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Seni Hiasan, Modern Decorative Arts of Modern Japan (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Yoshishige Saito (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Shu Takahashi (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Makoto Kakamura and Shigeo Fukuda (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Nozaki (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Sofu Teshigahara (Box 946, Folder 1)
    - Contemporary Polish Painters (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - Graphics by Esquimos of Canada, New Delhi, 1972 February 20-March 10 (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - Selected Paintings, Sculptures Graphics and Handicrafts from the Middle Asian Soviet Republics, 1973 November 29-December 13 (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - Abanindranath Togore and Some of His Disciples, 1971 August 7-September 10 (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - Loans from Private Collectors in Delhi, 1971 October 30-December 10 (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - Selected Paintings and Drawings by George Keyt (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - Selections from the Collection of the National Gallery of Modern Art, New Delhi (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - A Handbook of Paintings and Graphics, New Delhi (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - Computer Art (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - A Handbook of Sculptures (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - Dada (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - Narendra, 1972 June 21-July 21 (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - Modern Prints: Original Graphics by Picasso, Miro, Matisse, Braque, Chagall, de Kooning and Others (Box 946, Folder 2)
    - Festival of Indian Classical Dances, New Delhi, 1976 February 23-27 (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Hitoshi Nakazato, 1979 October 13-27 (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Toshinobu Onosato (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Kobashi (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Anne Truitt, 1964 October 19-31 (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Morita Shiryu, Work and Thought (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Koichi Tateishi (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Yamaguchi (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Arakawa (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Kumiko Imanaka Exhibition (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Shinjiro Okamoto Exhibition (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Jiro Takamatsu Exhibition, ?Identification (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Shoichi Ida (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Shoji Matsumoto (Box 946, Folder 3)
    - Shizuko Yoshikawa (Box 946, Folder 4)
    - Yusuke Nakahara (Box 946, Folder 4)
    - Hisao Domoto (Box 946, Folder 4)
    - Katsuro Yoshida (Box 946, Folder 4)
    - Sam Francis (Box 946, Folder 4)
    - Hitoshi Nakazato, 1977 November 10-26 (Box 946, Folder 4)
    - Xavier Cobero, 1966 September 9-30 (Box 946, Folder 4)
    - Kishio Suga (Box 946, Folder 4)
    - Kenzo Okada, 1965 October 20-November 28 (Box 946, Folder 4)
    - Hans Richter Exhibition, 1966 April 10-May 14 (Box 946, Folder 4)
    - Shuji Mizumoto (Box 946, Folder 4)
  - General Publications, 18.10
    - The Protection of Cultural Property, Handbook of National Legislations, Burnham, Bonnie, International Council of Museums (Box 947)
    - Master Plan for the Conservation of the Cultural Heritage in the Kathmandu Valley (Box 947)
    - Old Burma-Early Pagan (Box 947)
    - Building Conservation in Nepal, A Handbook of Principles and Techniques, John Sanday, 1978 (Box 947)
    - The Classical Tradition in Rajput Painting, Pratapaditya Pal (Box 947)
    - Museum Wayang, A Report on Ninety-Day Survey Travel to Europe, Asia and the USA (Box 948)
    - Candi, Fungsi Dan Pengertiannya (Box 948)
    - Dance Research Institute (Box 949, Folder 1)
    - Max Neuhaus - Time Pieces (Box 949, Folder 2)
    - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles, 1988 October 20 (Box 949, Folder 4)
    - Walker Art Center, Tokyo: Art and Spirit, 1986 April 20-July 20 (Box 949, Folder 5)
    - Publicity Materials (Box 949, Folder 6)
- Theater, 1964-2006; 19; 34.53 Cubic Feet 84 letter document boxes and 2 record storage boxes
  - Asia, 19.1
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, B-7347, 1973 (Box 858, Folder 6)
    - XIIth Congress of the International Theatre Institute of the United States (ITI), Theatre-Asia, Other than Correspondence, B-6725, 1967 (Box 858, Folder 7)
    - American National Theater Academy (ANTA), Seminar, DF-6706, 1967 (Box 858, Folder 8)
    - American Society for Eastern Arts, B-6949, 1969 (Box 858, Folder 9)
    - American Society for Theater Research, 6th Congress in International Federation for Theater Research, NYC, DF-7023, 1969 October 6-11 (Box 858, Folder 10)
    - AETA, Asian Theater Project, Film Lending Library System, B-7259, B-7346, 1972-1973 (Box 858, Folder 11)
    - International Theatre Institute (ITI), Theatre II Publications, DF-7090, 1970 (Box 859, Folder 1)
    - XIIth Congress of the International Theatre Institute (ITI), B-6725, 1967 (Box 859, Folder 2)
    - American Theatre Association, B-7884, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 3)
    - Brandon, James, B-7880, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 4)
    - Houghton, Norris, B-6666, DF-6750, 1966-1967 (Box 859, Folder 5)
    - International Theatre Institute, DF-8227, 1982 (Box 859, Folder 6)
    - International Theatre Institute, DF-8243, DF-8338, 1982-1983 (Box 859, Folder 7)
    - La MaMa Experimental Theatre Club, DF-8337, 1983 (Box 859, Folder 8)
    - Stewart, Ellen, DF-8023, 1980 (Box 859, Folder 9)
    - World Conference on Ritual and Theatre, DF-7939, DF-7944, DF7945, DF7958, DF-8025 (I), 1979-1980 (Box 860, Folder 1)
    - World Conference on Ritual and Theatre (II) (Box 860, Folder 2)
    - La MaMa Experimental Theatre Club, ITI, Korea, B-8105, 1981 (Box 860, Folder 3)
    - La MaMa Asian Theater Workshop, DF-8053, DF-8062, 1980 (Box 860, Folder 4)
    - International Center of Theatre Research, B-8737, 1987 (Box 860, Folder 5)
    - Reduta Deux, DF-8790, 1987 (Box 860, Folder 6)
    - Brandon, James R., B-88117(39)R, 1988 (Box 861, Folder 1)
    - Chong, Ping, 706-00-95063-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 861, Folder 2)
    - International Theater Institute, EC-8604, DF-92108, 100-00-94102-203.000-3, 1986-1994 (Box 861, Folder 3)
    - Mabou Mines, 100-00-96002-203.000-3, 1996 (Box 861, Folder 4)
    - Movement Theater International, EC-9107, 1991 (Box 861, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Mime Troupe, DF-9315, DF-9217, 100-00-94094-203.000-3, 1992-1994 (Box 861, Folder 6)
    - Shenandoah International Playwrights Retreat, 100-00-97111-203.3, 1997 (Box 862, Folder 1)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 100-00-97110-203.3, 1997 (Box 862, Folder 2)
    - Anthony, Vincent, 706-00-21092-203.1, 2001 (Box 862, Folder 3)
    - Asia Society, 100-00-99116-203.3, 1999 (Box 862, Folder 4)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 100-00-2118-203.3, 2001 (Box 862, Folder 5)
    - Committee for the Third Conference for Asian Women and Theatre, 704-00-20105-203.1, 2000 (Box 862, Folder 6)
    - Foley, Kathy, 707-00-21075-203.1, 2001 (Box 862, Folder 7)
    - Foley, Kathy and Michael Schuster, 706-00-98067-203.1, 1998 (Box 862, Folder 8)
    - Henson Foundation, B-9238, 1992 (Box 863, Folder 1)
    - Hensley, Charles, 706-00-21094-203.1, 2001 (Box 863, Folder 2)
    - Henson International Festival of Puppet Theater, 100-00-20057-203.1, 2000 (Box 863, Folder 3)
    - International Theatre Institute, 100-00-99001-203.3, 1999 (Box 863, Folder 4)
    - International Theatre Institute, 100-00-20005-203.3 (Box 863, Folder 5)
    - Theater Communications Group-ITI, 100-00-20155-203.1, 2000 (Box 863, Folder 6)
    - The Mysteries Foundation, 100-00-98109-203.3, 1998 (Box 863, Folder 7)
    - River Arts Repertory Company, 706-00-95069-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 864, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Nancy Stark, 100-00-99106-203.3, 1999 (Box 864, Folder 2)
    - Stewart, Ellen, JDR 3rd Award, 705-00-20160-203.1, 2000 (Box 864, Folder 3)
    - Theatreworks, Dreamtime, 100-00-21139-203.3, 2001 (Box 864, Folder 4)
    - Breuer, Lee, 100-00-22032-203.3, 2002 (Box 864, Folder 6)
    - Brown University, 702-00-25006-203.2, 2005 (Box 864, Folder 7)
    - Byrd Hoffman Water Mill Foundation, 100-00-24047-203.1, 2004 (Box 864, Folder 8)
    - Chumley, Daniel, 100-00-24052-203.3, 2004 (Box 864, Folder 9)
    - Practice Performing Arts School, 100-00-24048-203.1, 2004 (Box 864, Folder 10)
    - Sacharow, Lawrence, 706-00-25008-203.2, 2005 (Box 865, Folder 1)
    - Theatre Communications Group-ITI, 100-00-25034-203.3, 2005 (Box 865, Folder 2)
    - Theatreworks, 100-00-20133-203.3, 2000 (Box 865, Folder 3)
  - Bangladesh, 19.2
    - Huda, Quazi Moshoorul, DF-8329, 1983 (Box 865, Folder 4)
    - Rashid, Maunur, 100-00-95102-203.000-3, 1995 (Box 865, Folder 5)
  - Bhutan, 19.3
    - University of Massachusetts, 702-00-99063-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 865, Folder 6)
  - Cambodia, 19.4
    - Cravath, Paul, DF-7579, 1975 (Box 865, Folder 7)
    - Direction Des Arts Et Spectacles, 100-00-95100-203.000-3, 1995 (Box 866, Folder 1)
    - Frumberg, Fred, 100-00-99140-203.1, 1999 (Box 866, Folder 2)
    - La MaMa, E.T.C., 100-00-22015-203.2, 2002 (Box 866, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Clifton, 100-00-22063-203.1, 2002 (Box 866, Folder 4)
    - Tipton, Jennifer, 100-00-21071-203.1, 2001 (Box 866, Folder 5)
    - Amrita Performing Arts, 100-00-24128-203.3, 2004 (Box 866, Folder 6)
    - Amrita Performing Arts, Support Phase I and II Bassac-Peking Opera Exchange Project (Box 866, Folder 7)
    - Filloux, Catherine, 100-00-20158-203.1, 2000 (Box 866, Folder 8)
    - Filloux, Catherine, 100-00-20158-203.1, 2000 (Box 867, Folder 1)
    - Frumberg, Fred, 100-00-215555-203.1, 100-00-221556-203.3, 2001-2002 (Box 867, Folder 2)
    - Kosal, Mann, 718-00-24016-203.2, 2004 (Box 867, Folder 3)
    - Oum, Suphany, 718-00-24093-203.1, 2004 (Box 868, Folder 1)
    - Conceison, Claire, 706-00-21095-203.1, 2001 (Box 868, Folder 2)
  - China, 19.5
    - City Center of Music and Drama, Inc., Wu Shu Troupe, DF-7490, 1974 (Box 868, Folder 3)
    - City Center of Music and Drama, Inc., Shenyang Acrobatic Troupe of China, DF-7382, 1973 (Box 868, Folder 4)
    - City Center of Music and Drama, Wu Schu Troupe, DF-7490, 1974 (Box 868, Folder 5)
    - Shenyang Acrobatic Troupe of China, DF-7382, 1973 (Box 868, Folder 6)
    - Asia Society, Fujian Hand Puppets, DF-8052, 1980 (Box 868, Folder 7)
    - Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, B-8418, 1984 (Box 868, Folder 8)
    - Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, DF-8724, DF-8782, 1987 (Box 868, Folder 9)
    - SUNY-Buffalo, 1st International Women Playwrights Conference, B-8843, 1988 (Box 869, Folder 1)
    - Yu, Shan, Df-86115, B-8731, EC-8899, 1986-1988 (Box 869, Folder 2)
    - Cheng, Meiling, B-9236, B-9124, B-9027, B-8924, B-8832, 1988-1992 (Box 869, Folder 3-4)
    - Pickle Family Circus, B-9021, 1990 (Box 869, Folder 5)
    - Schechner, Richard, B-8753(56)R, 1987 (Box 870, Folder 1)
    - Booker, Margaret, Beijing People?s Art Theater, 479-00-96037-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 870, Folder 2)
    - Breuer, Lee, DF-9317, 1993 (Box 870, Folder 3)
    - Duchesne, Isabelle, 704-00-96121-203.1, 1996 (Box 870, Folder 4)
    - Coigney, Martha, ITI, ITI Beijing Conference, DF-9177, 1991 (Box 870, Folder 5)
    - Falk, Heinrich Richard, B-92103(56), 1992 (Box 870, Folder 6)
    - New York University, 100-00-94111-203.000-3, 1994 (Box 870, Folder 7)
    - Nichols, A. Richard, 479-00-94116-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 870, Folder 8)
    - Rong, Guang Run, DF-9311, 451-00-94048-203.000-1, 1994 (Box 871, Folder 1)
    - Sun, William and Kopit, Arthur, 100-00-96031-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 871, Folder 2)
    - Tufts University, Beijing Opera Teacher Res., Fan, Yisong, 100-00-940006-203.000-2, 1994 (Box 871, Folder 3)
    - U. S. Institute for Theater Technology, 100-00-94103-203.000-3, 1994 (Box 871, Folder 4)
    - Vasilevski, Valeria, China Conservatory of Music, 479-00-96039-203.000-1, 1996 (Box 871, Folder 5)
    - Asia Society, 100-00-99047-203.1, 1999 (Box 871, Folder 6)
    - Cao, Lu Sheng, 702-00-97057-203.000-1, 702-00-94033-203.000-1, B-9341, B-9250, B-9031, 1990-1997 (Box 871, Folder 7)
    - Conceison, Claire A., 706-00-95065-203.000-1, 1995 (Box 872, Folder 1)
    - Evans, Anne Megan, 706-00-980707-203.1, 1998 (Box 872, Folder 2)
    - Elder, Eldon, B-9363(56), DF-8793, 1987 (Box 872, Folder 3)
    - Gao, Xingjian, DF-8915, 1989 (Box 872, Folder 4)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 100-00-99048-203.1, 1999 (Box 872, Folder 5)
    - Ren, Ming, 587-00-99066-203.000-1, 1999 (Box 872, Folder 6)
    - Rong, Guangrun, 100-00-21040-203.3, 2001 (Box 872, Folder 7)